

Larysa Skrypkina

JUNIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER

Details

991209873

larysa.skrypkin@gmail.com

Links

Resume

linkedin

<u>github</u>

online library

image-finder project

KidsLike project

statistic charts

card list

Skills

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

React

Redux

Adobe Photoshop

GitHub

Languages

English

Hebrew

Profile

Results-oriented Junior Front End Developer dedicated to creating and optimizing interactive, user-friendly, and feature-rich websites and apps.

Half a year ago after successfully finishing my education and accomplishing several pet projects I landed a job in start-up company.

I have used core JS, React, Redux. I've also mastered HTML5 & CSS3.

I have experience of agile methodology and working within Jira and Trello.

I have experience in conducting communications with English native speakers in both written and verbal form.

Employment History

Junior Front End Developer, VTlabs, Kiev

FEBRUARY 2020 - JULY 2020

Creating modular, responsive sites and apps using modern CSS techniques and JavaScript libraries.

Collaborating with designers to ensure designs were efficient and technically sound.

Implementing a mobile-first approach to existing websites.

Building stable and maintainable codebases using React.

Beta QA, Nova Pochta, Kiev

MAY 2017 - DECEMBER 2017

Designing and performing positive and negative test cases to ensure compliance with the customers' requirements

Working with test management system TestRail

Documented issues in the bug tracking system JIRA

Accountant, Taam Teva Altman, Israel, Tel Aviv

2009 - DECEMBER 2013

Coordinate the activities of the accounting staff

Developed and implemented schedules pertaining to the preparation of account books

Conducted internal checks prior to the audit to resolve any discrepancies

Prepared bi-annual statements and filed tax statements

Performed all other activities falling under the jurisdiction of my job responsibilities

Education

GoIT, Kiev

FEBRUARY 2018 - OCTOBER 2019

Full stack Certificate (HTML+CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Node.js)

Yurij Chernigorcev IT-school, Kiev

JANUARY 2017 - APRIL 2017

Software testing Certificate, 2017

DECEMBER 2019 - DECEMBER 2019